<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-10-28T20:33:04-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">How to Screenshot a Snap Without Anyone Knowing</title><link href="/2017/06/30/how-to-screenshot-a-snap-without-anyone-knowing-copy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Screenshot a Snap Without Anyone Knowing" /><published>2017-06-30T23:59:49-04:00</published><updated>2017-06-30T23:59:49-04:00</updated><id>/2017/06/30/how-to-screenshot-a-snap-without-anyone-knowing%20copy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/06/30/how-to-screenshot-a-snap-without-anyone-knowing-copy.html">&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Snapchat is a popular social media service that allows you to send photos and videos that supposedly disappear once a certain period of time is elapsed. Of course, sometimes, you receive a snap that you want to save forever, so you screenshot it. However, screenshotting a snap sends a notification to the original sender, which notifies them of your screenshot. So how do you get around that limitation? You follow this guide, which uses a flaw in Snapchat's screenshot detection system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tutorial may seem like a lot to remember at first, but you can always come back here to make sure you remember everything. Also, it gets a lot easier once you've done it a lot, and you end up breaking it down to about 4 steps, which I've included at the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Things You'll Need&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iOS device&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snapchat app&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;tutorialguide&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open Snapchat, and determine which snap you want to screenshot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you've already opened the snap you want to save, just let the time run out, then tap and hold on the snap to use a Replay on it. Do not open the replayed snap yet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make sure the snap is loaded. You will know the snap is loaded when it says &quot;Tap to view&quot; under the contact name, instead of &quot;Tap to load&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 3&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Turn on Airplane mode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 4&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Open the snap and screenshot it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 5&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Press and hold the power button until you see &quot;Slide to power off&quot;. DO NOT POWER DOWN OR LOCK THE DEVICE, OR THE NOTIFICATION WILL GO THROUGH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 6&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Press and hold the home button (as if you're trying to summon Siri) until Snapchat &quot;crashes&quot; to the homescreen. If it looks like it's about to &quot;crash&quot;, but Snapchat opens immediately, repeat this step until you've either done it at least 4 or 5 times, or it crashes to the homescreen, whichever happens first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following steps 5 and 6 in any app on iOS apparently clears the cache or the device's RAM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 7&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Turn off Airplane mode, and wait for your Internet connection to reconnect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 8&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Open Snapchat and verify that no screenshot has been sent. You should also be able to view the screenshotted snap as if you had never opened it (once everything loads). If you see that a screenshot has been sent, then you most likely messed up either step 5 or step 6.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;4 Step Guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;tutorialguide&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open Snapchat, and load the snap you want to save&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turn on Airplane mode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 3&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Screenshot the snap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 4&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Do the power button cache/RAM clear trick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's it, you've screenshotted a snap without anyone knowing! If you like these tutorials or you want to hear more from me, please follow me on Twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.twitter.com/JustinAlexP&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@JustinAlexP&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This guide is heavily based on some of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/EverythingApplePro&quot;&gt;EverythingApplePro&lt;/a&gt;'s videos, with some clarification added by me.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Introduction Snapchat is a popular social media service that allows you to send photos and videos that supposedly disappear once a certain period of time is elapsed. Of course, sometimes, you receive a snap that you want to save forever, so you screenshot it. However, screenshotting a snap sends a notification to the original sender, which notifies them of your screenshot. So how do you get around that limitation? You follow this guide, which uses a flaw in Snapchat's screenshot detection system. This tutorial may seem like a lot to remember at first, but you can always come back here to make sure you remember everything. Also, it gets a lot easier once you've done it a lot, and you end up breaking it down to about 4 steps, which I've included at the end.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Install App Store Apps Without the App Store</title><link href="/2017/06/30/how-to-install-app-atore-apps-without-the-app-store.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Install App Store Apps Without the App Store" /><published>2017-06-30T23:59:49-04:00</published><updated>2017-06-30T23:59:49-04:00</updated><id>/2017/06/30/how-to-install-app-atore-apps-without-the-app-store</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/06/30/how-to-install-app-atore-apps-without-the-app-store.html">&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The App Store is the go-to download center for every iPhone, iPad and iPod touch user. However, iOS allows administrators to disable access to the App Store through MDM profiles and the restrictions settings. Some MDM profiles cannot be removed, and other management profiles send a notification to the administrator when they are removed. This means that you might not be able to install apps on your device. In some of these cases, &lt;a href=&quot;how_to_bypass_restrictions_password_on_ios.html&quot;&gt;you could just bypass the restrictions password&lt;/a&gt;, but if you don't want to, then this guide is for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've written this guide using a Mac, so steps might be a little different for Windows users, though it should still be very similar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Things You'll Need&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Internet connection with access to Apple's iTunes servers (if you want to download apps) and file.io (if your school or your parents block either one of these, then you can go to Walmart or a public library or something).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an iOS device and either a Mac, or a Windows PC with iTunes 12.6.3 installed. If you don't have iTunes installed, or have a newer version, you can download it &lt;a href=&quot;https://support.apple.com/en-ca/HT208079&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;tutorialguide&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open iTunes on your computer, and switch to the Apps section using the drop-down menu under the media controls in the top
left hand corner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Switch to the App Store tab of iTunes, using the menu in the middle of the same control bar that the drop-down menu was in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 3&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Download the app(s) you want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 4&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Switch back to the &quot;Library&quot; tab of iTunes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 5&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Right click on the app you'd like to install.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 6&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;On macOS, click &quot;Show in Finder&quot;. It should say &quot;Show in Windows Explorer&quot; on Windows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 7&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Go to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dropbox.com&quot;&gt;the Dropbox website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 8&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Make an account if you don't already have one, then log in. If you already have an account, just log in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 9&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Drag and drop the .ipa file iTunes highlighted in Finder or Windows Explorer into your Dropbox, in the folder you want 
it to be in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 10&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Hover over the file listing to show the &quot;Share&quot; button.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 11&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Click the &quot;Share&quot; button.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 12&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;There should be a blue &quot;Show Link&quot; link somewhere on the page. Click it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 13&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;The link should be shown. Copy it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 14&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Paste the link somewhere (in TextEdit/Notepad, or even in your browser's navigation bar).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 15&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;The link should end in &quot;dl=0&quot;. Change the 0 to a 1, so it ends with &quot;dl=1&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 16&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Send that link to yourself, whether by email, iMessage, or some other means.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 17&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Download Saurik's Impactor from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cydiaimpactor.com&quot;&gt;its official website&lt;/a&gt;. Don't worry, it's safe 
(as of the writing of this tutorial, June 30th, 2017).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make sure you download it for the operating system you're using. If you're using a Mac, it's probably macOS. Otherwise, it's probably Windows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 18&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Download the latest version of App Installer from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Sn0wCh1ld/App-Installer&quot;&gt;official GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 19&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Open Impactor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 20&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Plug in your iOS device. If you're using Windows, wait for the drivers to install.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 21&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Once Impactor recognizes your device, drag and drop the .ipa file for App Installer that you downloaded to the textbox
that has your device's name in it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 22&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;You will have to put in your Apple ID and password. Put it in. It's safe, as of June 30th, 2017.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 23&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;If you are subscribed to the Apple Developer Program, there may be a box telling you to choose which certificate to use. Choose one. If you are not, or you don't know, skip this step.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 24&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Wait for the app to install. If there's a plist error of some kind, ignore it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 25&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Open App Installer from your home screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 26&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;There's a text field in the middle of the screen. Copy the link you sent yourself earlier, and paste it in the text 
field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 27&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Press the &quot;Install&quot; button.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 28&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Wait for a message saying something along the lines of &quot;file.io would like to install App Installer&quot; to pop up. Press 
&quot;Install&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 29&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Go back to your home screen, and wait for the app to install, then open it.&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;While it's installing, make sure you're 
logged into the App Store with the same account that you used to download the app on your computer. You can check this in 
the Settings app under the &quot;iTunes and App Store&quot; section. If you're not logged in, log in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 30&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;When you open the app, there may be a dialog box asking you to put in your Apple ID and password. Enter your Apple ID 
credentials. This is 100% safe as long as you &lt;i&gt;did&lt;/i&gt; download the app directly from Apple using iTunes. The app should 
finish opening with no problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's it, you've downloaded an App Store app without using the App Store on your iOS device! If you like these tutorials or you 
want to hear more from me, please follow me on Twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.twitter.com/JustinAlexP&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@JustinAlexP&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Introduction The App Store is the go-to download center for every iPhone, iPad and iPod touch user. However, iOS allows administrators to disable access to the App Store through MDM profiles and the restrictions settings. Some MDM profiles cannot be removed, and other management profiles send a notification to the administrator when they are removed. This means that you might not be able to install apps on your device. In some of these cases, you could just bypass the restrictions password, but if you don't want to, then this guide is for you. I've written this guide using a Mac, so steps might be a little different for Windows users, though it should still be very similar.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Bypass AdBlock Blockers</title><link href="/2017/05/13/how-to-bypass-adblock-blockers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Bypass AdBlock Blockers" /><published>2017-05-13T21:58:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-05-13T21:58:00-04:00</updated><id>/2017/05/13/how-to-bypass-adblock-blockers</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/05/13/how-to-bypass-adblock-blockers.html">&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether it's Adblock Plus, uBlock Origin, or some other content blocker, having an ad blocker on is always a good idea. It increases the security on your computer by blocking potentially malicious ads and other undesirable content, and makes websites look and feel cleaner all while making them load faster, among other things. However, some websites don't like when you block their ads, and in return, they don't allow you to see their content. But what if you want to read those articles without compromising your security or convenience? This tutorial is here to help. I'll update it if I come across new methods to get around the problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If any method works for you, you don't really need to read the rest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Things You'll Need&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your computer (some of these may work on mobile devices though)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;tutorialguide&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Temporarily disable Javascript&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some websites detect adblockers by running some javascript, so disabling it may fix your issue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each browser is different, but in my main browser, Safari, it is done by first enabling the Devloper menu. This is done by going to Safari Preferences (Safari menu bar button, then preferences), then to Advanced, then ticking the checkbox that says &quot;Show Develop menu in menu bar&quot;. Close that window, then in the menu bar, open the Develop menu, and click on Disable Javascript. When you're done with the website, re-enable Javascript by going back to the Develop menu, and clicking Disable Javascript again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can follow &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wikihow.com/Disable-JavaScript&quot;&gt;this WikiHow article&lt;/a&gt; to learn how to disable javascript in some other browsers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Temporarily disable CSS (works on Forbes.com)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Forbes.com and probably other websites, all you have to do is disable CSS and click the right link.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each browser is different, but in my main browser, Safari, it is done by first enabling the Devloper menu. This is done by going to Safari Preferences (Safari menu bar button, then preferences), then to Advanced, then ticking the checkbox that says &quot;Show Develop menu in menu bar&quot;. Close that window, then in the menu bar, open the Develop menu, and click on Disable Styles. Next, (on Forbes), wait for the &quot;disable AdBlock&quot; popup to appear, and click &quot;continue to site&quot;. Then you can re-enable CSS by going back to the Develop menu, and clicking Disable Styles again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Use inspect element to remove the &quot;disable AdBlock&quot; overlay&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, all you have to do is delete the offending part of the website. Right click on the page, and click &quot;Inspect Element&quot;. Every modern browser should have a similar function. Inspect Element will come up, and you have to select the &quot;Select&quot; tool. It usually looks like a crosshair or a mouse by a window. Hover over the overlay, and it should light up. Click it. Inside Inspect Element, some HTML should now be highlighted. Click the delete key on your keyboard. If it doesn't work, try deleting other things that may be part of the overlay. Make sure you don't delete the main content!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Use AdBlock Plus' Block Element feature&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;I'm not sure if other blockers have this, but AdBlock Plus has a Block Element feature that acts similarly to the Inspect Element method I just talked about. Click the &quot;Block Element&quot; button in the AdBlock Plus menu and then click on the overlay. A new tab should open up asking if you want to block that element. Say yes. You can undo it later by going to the &quot;Options&quot; section under the AdBlock Plus menu, then to &quot;Add your own filters&quot;, and from there, removing the blocked elements from the list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully my methods worked for you! I'll update the guide if I discover a new way to get around the AdBlock blockers. If you like these tutorials or you want to hear more from me, please follow me on Twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.twitter.com/JustinAlexP&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@JustinAlexP&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Introduction Whether it's Adblock Plus, uBlock Origin, or some other content blocker, having an ad blocker on is always a good idea. It increases the security on your computer by blocking potentially malicious ads and other undesirable content, and makes websites look and feel cleaner all while making them load faster, among other things. However, some websites don't like when you block their ads, and in return, they don't allow you to see their content. But what if you want to read those articles without compromising your security or convenience? This tutorial is here to help. I'll update it if I come across new methods to get around the problem. If any method works for you, you don't really need to read the rest.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Bypass OurPact</title><link href="/2017/01/03/how-to-bypass-ourpact.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Bypass OurPact" /><published>2017-01-03T01:08:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-01-03T01:08:00-05:00</updated><id>/2017/01/03/how-to-bypass-ourpact</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/01/03/how-to-bypass-ourpact.html">&lt;h2&gt;Note&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As of February 3rd, 2017, the workarounds may have been patched in a newer version of OurPact than was used to develop this guide. Though the profile will still be removed, granting you freedom on your device, if the patch works, then the notification and email will unfortunately not be stopped. I hope it still works, but as an OurPact developer &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/teenagers/comments/5lqd6y/figured_some_of_you_guys_parents_might_have/dd9e5iw/?context=3&quot;&gt;said on Reddit&lt;/a&gt;, use at your own risk.&lt;p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OurPact is a tool that allows parents to take near-absolute control over their children's devices. I've personally never been subjected to it, but I've met people who have had it installed on their phones, and I really felt bad for them. I've come to despise the program, and I want to help anyone controlled by it to have a way out. Here are two guides to beating OurPact, each with increasing difficulty, but also with increasing effectiveness. The guides are only for iOS devices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first guide should remove OurPact your iOS device without notifying the parent. Effective against most parents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second guide should remove OurPact your iOS device without notifying the parent. It will also add a new profile that looks like the official OurPact profile. If a parent checked their child's Settings app, they would not be easily able to tell the profile had been tampered with. Effective against most curious/relatively tech savvy/relatively untrusting parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Things You'll Need&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your iOS device&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Shorter Guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;tutorialguide&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enable Airplane mode on your device.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the Settings app, navigate to General &amp;gt; Device Management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 3&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Select &quot;Device System Profile&quot;, with the name &quot;OurPact&quot; underneath it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 4&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Press &quot;Remove Management&quot; and put in your password. When prompted, press remove.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 5&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Once the profile is removed, press the home button and power button until you see an Apple logo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 6&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;When the device is booted back up, unlock it, turn off Airplane mode, and hope it worked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;More Effective Guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;tutorialguide&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On your iOS device, copy &lt;a href=&quot;https://royalapps.xyz/Files/ourhact.mobileconfig&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; link and send it to yourself (preferably using the Messages app).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enable Airplane mode on your device.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 3&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;In the Settings app, navigate to General &amp;gt; Device Management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 4&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Select &quot;Device System Profile&quot;, with the name &quot;OurPact&quot; underneath it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 5&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Press &quot;Remove Management&quot; and put in your password. When prompted, press remove.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 6&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Once the profile is removed, press the home button and power button until you see an Apple logo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 7&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;When the device is booted back up, unlock it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 8&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Go to the Messages app and copy the link you sent yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 9&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Go to Safari, and paste the link in the navigation bar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 10&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Before pressing &quot;Go&quot;, disable Airplane mode and wait for your device to connect to Wi-Fi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 11&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Press go, and wait for the Settings app to pop up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 12&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Press install, and go through the installation process (you will have to put in your password).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 13&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Hope it worked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 14&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Go back to the Messages app and delete the message(s) containing the link you sent yourself. Do the same on other devices that also receive your messages. You can also delete the entire conversation with yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully my guides worked for you! If you like these tutorials or you want to hear more from me, please follow me on Twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.twitter.com/JustinAlexP&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@JustinAlexP&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I worked pretty hard developing these methods, but I when I got stumped, I searched around a little and found &lt;a href=&quot;https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20160607095601AAjFnpt&quot;&gt;this Yahoo Answers post&lt;/a&gt;. User Jai's answer helped quite a bit with the actual bypassing of OurPact, so I'd just like to give credit. All the rest of the material in this guide is original.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Note As of February 3rd, 2017, the workarounds may have been patched in a newer version of OurPact than was used to develop this guide. Though the profile will still be removed, granting you freedom on your device, if the patch works, then the notification and email will unfortunately not be stopped. I hope it still works, but as an OurPact developer said on Reddit, use at your own risk.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Bypass the Restrictions Password on iOS</title><link href="/2017/01/02/how-to-bypass-restrictions-password-ios.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Bypass the Restrictions Password on iOS" /><published>2017-01-02T10:38:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-01-02T10:38:00-05:00</updated><id>/2017/01/02/how-to-bypass-restrictions-password-ios</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/01/02/how-to-bypass-restrictions-password-ios.html">&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With iOS, Apple includes a number of parental control tools, which can be used to disable or limit many iOS functions. But what if you accidentally lock yourself out on your own device, someone else adds one to your device without your permission, or you add one on purpose, but forget the password? The solution is simple; you need to crack the password. This tutorial will teach you exactly how this is done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Things You'll Need&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your iOS device&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A computer with Internet connection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;tutorialguide&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Download iBackupBot to your computer from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.icopybot.com/download.htm&quot;&gt;this website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Install, then run it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 3&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Select your device, then navigate to &lt;code&gt;System Files/HomeDomain/Library/Preferences/com.apple.restrictionspassword.plist&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 4&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Find &lt;code&gt;RestrictionsPasswordKey&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;RestrictionsPasswordSalt&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 5&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Go to &lt;a href=&quot;http://1024kb.co.nz/ios-7-8-9-10-passcode-hack/&quot;&gt;this webpage&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 6&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;At the bottom of the webpage, there are four fields: RestrictionsPasswordKey, RestrictionsPasswordSalt, Starting Passcode and End Passcode. Put the info from iBackupBot (RestrictionsPasswordKey and RestrictionsPasswordSalt) in the appropriate field. If you know the password is higher and/or lower than a certain number, you can set up the Starting Passcode and End Passcode fields. If you don't have any clue, or you don't know what those fields do, then just leave them at 0000 and 9999, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 7&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Wait for the website to get the password. Do not leave the webpage. Leave the webpage open, do not switch screens to go to a different app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While you wait, you can follow me on Twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.twitter.com/JustinAlexP&quot;&gt;@JustinAlexP&lt;/a&gt; for more tech stuff, and updates when new tutorials come out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 8&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Once the website has found the password, use it to unlock, and then disable or change your restrictions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's it, you've broken into the restrictions on iOS! If you like these tutorials or you want to hear more from me, please follow me on Twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.twitter.com/JustinAlexP&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@JustinAlexP&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Introduction With iOS, Apple includes a number of parental control tools, which can be used to disable or limit many iOS functions. But what if you accidentally lock yourself out on your own device, someone else adds one to your device without your permission, or you add one on purpose, but forget the password? The solution is simple; you need to crack the password. This tutorial will teach you exactly how this is done.</summary></entry></feed>